superstoker.com 2013-05-02

# Privacy Policy » STOKED

Stoked.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to facilitate the provision of our online services and to provide you with a more personalized experience. We have created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of all of our clients.   
We are also careful to ensure that information is used responsibly, and only for the purposes for which it is provided.   
This Privacy Policy is intended to comply with the federal government’s privacy legislation, the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, as well as British Columbia’s Personal Information Protection Act.  We want you to understand how and under what circumstances your personal information is collected, used and disclosed, as well as what Stoked.com is doing to ensure that your information is used according to good business practices and is protected accordingly.   
What is Personal Information?   
Personal information is information that identifies you as an individual.  It includes information such as your name, address, telephone number, birth date, social insurance number, e-mail address and financial information.   
The information we may collect or obtain includes but may not be limited to:   
Full name and email address   
Personal Information Collection and Use by Stoked.com   
We collect your personal information in order to contact you, to understand your needs and preferences, to better provide our services and to meet statutory or legal obligations.  In all circumstances we try to limit our collection of personal information to only those items that are necessary in order for us to provide the best service to our customers.   
Stoked.com does not collect personal information about you without your knowledge and consent.   
Personal Information Disclosure by Stoked.com   
We will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent to do so.  Stoked.com reserves the right to disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims or to protect the rights, property or safety of Stoked.com, its customers or the public.   
When Do We Share Your Personal Information   
There are some circumstances where we may share some personal information about our users with a third party.  For example:   
1.            Your personal information may be disclosed to a company or individual employed by Stoked.com to perform functions on our behalf such as data processing or document retention.  Any such disclosure of your personal information is made on a strictly confidential basis, and the information is to be used only for the purpose for which it was shared.  Stoked.com ensures that the company or individual adheres to this Privacy Policy.   
2.            Subject to applicable regulations, we may disclose your personal information to a government agency, court, or law enforcement  personnel.   
It is Stoked.com’s policy NOT to sell its customer or member database to any third party.   
Personal Information Protection by Stoked.com   
We recognize our obligations to protect personal information.  We have therefore made arrangements to secure against the unauthorized access, collection, use, disclosure, copying, modification and disposal of personal information.   
Stoked.com considers personal information provided by you to be private and confidential and accordingly we treat it with care.   
Consent to Use of Personal Information   
By submitting personal information to Stoked.com, you acknowledge and agree that you have consented to the collection, use and disclosure practices set out in this Privacy Policy as they relate to your personal information.  You may withdraw your consent at any time by contacting Stoked.com’s privacy officer as set out below.   
Accessing, Correcting or Updating Your Personal Information   
At any time, you may request that we correct or update your personal information by contacting Stoked.com’s privacy officer as set out below.  Stoked.com will use reasonable efforts to ensure that your personal information is accurate and current.   
Contacting Stoked.com   
If you have any requests, questions or comments about your personal information or this Privacy Policy, you may contact us in one of the following ways:   
By email:       contact@stoked.com   
This Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time without notice.  Revisions will be posted on Stoked.com’s website at http://www.Stoked.com.  This Privacy Policy is dated September 10th, 2010.
